Put her there, you old so-and-so.
Well, uh... I'm gonna see you
at work in 12 hours.
(Howard:)Don't you think
it could have waited until then?
(Sheldon:)Holy smoke,
why didn't I think of that?
(Sheldon:)You're a better man than I,
Howard wolowitz.
You put her there, you son of a gun.
Whatever. Heh.
(Hot girl:)My...
(Leonard:)It's...
Oh, my God, Howie!
What did you do?
(Sheldon:)It was a harmless Halloween prank.
Look.
(Bernadette:)Howard has a heart condition.
You know that.
(Sheldon:)Well, I thought he made that up.
(Sheldon:)Isn't hypochondria a common
idiosyncrasy of Jewish people?
(Bernadette:)This is adrenaline.
We're gonna inject it into his heart.
- We are?
- You are. I'm not strong enough...
(Bernadette:)...to get it through his chest plate
and we've only got one shot.
Oh, no, I can't!